# Shah Shivam

### Full-Stack Java, Web Developer

Address Ahmedabad, Gujarat, 380001

**Phone** 9664858715

**E-mail** shivamshah.glsbca20@gmail.com

**LinkedIn** https://www.linkedin.com/in/shah-shivam

**WWW** https://github.com/shi-vam7902

Dedicated IT Professional with work history of **0.6 Years** in Web-Development. With **MEAN-MERN Stack**. Also have an excellent communication skills whenever needed with best Judgement.

seeking forward for more industry in the very beginning of career

in Java Frameworks.

References available required.

# **Programming Languages**

- C
- C++
- Java(Version 8)
- Python

### **Front-end Development**

- Java Script
- HTML[5]
- CSS
- Bootstrap [version 4]

### **Technologies and Frameworks**

- Bootstrap 4
- Servlet
- JSP
- Node JS
- Express
- Angular(8)
- Android(Java)
- REST API Building
- Spring(WEB MVC)
- Spring Boot

#### **Databases and Other Tools**

- Oracle (Version 11)
- MySql(Version 5.8)
- Mongo DB
- Postgresql

#### **Tools And IDE's**

- Postman (Version 10.12)
- Android Studio (Bumblebee)
- Eclipse
- Visual Studio Code
- GitHub- Version Control
- Mongo DB Compass
- MySql WorkBench
- Apache Tomcat Server
- Heroku Deployment
- Maven
- Gradle (Android)
- PgAdmin
- phpMyAdmin

### **Work History**

2022-06 - Current

#### Intern

Unnati Informatics LLP, Kargil-Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- Worked with back-end developers to design APIs.
- Developed functional databases, applications and servers to support websites on back-end.
- Collaborated with team members gave efficient input

#### 2022-05 - 2022-06

### Internship Student

NIT Trichy National Institute of Technology, Tiruchirappalli, Remote-Ahmedabad, Gujarat

• Interacted with Colleagues by phone, email or in-person to provide information.

#### 2020-07 - 2020-11

#### Intern

Royal Tecnosoft Private limited, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- Coordinated With senior faculties for practicing C and C++ JAVA towards Students logic building.
- Resolved Technical and Logical issues and Helped Them out.
- Upgraded to new Technologies with senior developers and faculties.

#### **Education**

2017-06 - 2018-04

SSC: Secondary School Certificate.

St Blaze English - Maninagar Ahmedabad

Completed SSC With Securing Grade B

2019-06 - 2020-03

**HSC: Higher Secondary School Certificate** 

Divine Buds High School - Uttamnagar Ahmedabad

- Elected Vice-Captain of Cricket Team.
- concluded with Grade B

2020-06 - Current

Bachelor of Computer Applications: Computer And Information Sciences

GLS University - CG Road Ahmedabad

## **Project 1**

- 1. DPharma
- Description
- D\_Pharmaceuticals is an established pharmaceutical based at Gujarat. We are into Franchisee marketing of (Finished Dosage Formulations) & have own Marketing, Sales, Distribution team at Gujarat. We Ethically promote the scientific products to various specialties such as., Dermatologists, Gynecologists, Pediatrics, General Medicine, Surgeons, Orthopaedicians, Cardiologists, Diabetologists etc., We strongly believe in Quality & ensure that all the products are FDA certified.
- Roles and Responsibility
- Managed the Bootstrap for contact us page, login, signups
- Worked with Component Structure
- Environment
- Angular ,Html , Css ,Js
- https://dpharma-cfb92.web.app/

# **Project 2**

#### **Eholiday**

- Description
- A travel website for basic managing portal for admin
- Performing and maintaining the crud operations from backend
- Environment
- Advance java(J2EE), Servlet, JSP, BootStrap
- link- https://eholiday.herokuapp.com

# Certifications

2020-01	[Programming], [Royal Tecnosoft Private Limited] - [C Programming]
2020-07	[Internship] -C
2021-05	[Game Development], [Royal Tecnosoft Private ]
2021-05	[Back-end], [Royal Tecnosoft Private ] -[Python]
2020-08	[CodeExpress-7], [GLS University] - [C,C++]
2022-08	[Code Express], [Gls University] - [MongoDb]
2022-02	[Hackathon], [Sharda University-IEEE] - [Smart Safety and Security]
2022-02	[International Webinar], [FCAIT] - [Tickle Your Mind]
2022-08	[Adv-java-Back-end] , [Royal Tecnosoft Private Limited] - [J2EE]
2022-09	[Application Development], [Royal Tecnosoft Private Limited] - [Android]

# **Languages Known**

- English (Fluent)
- Gujarati
- Hindi